Thor Wessel Lindberg

CONTACT

Copenhagen, Denmark thorlindberg@icloud.com

thorlindberg.com apple.com/developer/thor-lindberg

ABOUT ME

I'm a 25-year old junior developer and digital designer, passionate about design systems, software architecture, and mobile applications.

For the past 4+ years I have been writing in object-oriented programming languages, and the past 1+ year I have been developing eventand state-driven software projects.

LANGUAGES

Swift, JavaScript, TypeScript, Python, Java, Visual Basic for Applications, Lua, SQL, XML

TOOLS

Xcode, Visual Studio Code, Git, GitLab, Figma, Excel, Tableau, Cytoscape

FRAMEWORKS

SwiftUI, UIKit, SceneKit, ARKit, VisionKit, Streamlit, React, Bootstrap

EDUCATION

MSc Information Technology (cand.it)

IT-University of Copenhagen, 2020-2022

BSc Health Information Science (bach.sund.it) Copenhagen University, 2017-2020

EXPERIENCE

IT Administrator, Financial Intelligence Unit Special Crime Unit, 2021-2022

Assistant Lecturer, Introduction to Programming IT-University of Copenhagen, 2022

Assistant Lecturer, UX Design II IT-University of Copenhagen, 2022

Teaching Assistant, UX Design I IT-University of Copenhagen, 2022

Teaching Assistant, Experimental Design IT-University of Copenhagen, 2022

Teaching Assistant, Introduction to Programming *IT-University of Copenhagen, 2021*

Store Leader, Domino's Pizza Domino's Lyngby, 2021-2022